Who the hell are you?
Quem é você?
Jered.
Jered.
I'm a monk of the Angels.
Um servo dos Anjos.
I'm not going to the cathedral.
Eu não vou para a catedral.
I'm trying to rescue you!
Eu estou tentando resgatá-la!
“All who follow the Light shall shun him, and bring him before the Angels for his judgement and cleansing.”
“Aqueles que seguem a Luz devem levá-lo aos Anjos para que seja julgado e purificado."
It's wrong!
Está errado!
Don't let him escape!
Não o deixem escapar!
You will bring him to Me, will you not?
Você o trará até mim, não é?
How dare you come in here, you little bastard?
Como você se atreve a vir aqui, maldito?
All right.
Muito bem.
You win.
Você venceu.
I'll come back.
Eu voltarei.
Oh faithful servant...
Oh, servo fiel..
Bring to Me My sacrifice.
Traga-Me Minha oferenda.
Lord...
Senhor...
Say what is your will.
Diga a sua vontade.
There are three here to be chosen.
Há três aqui para serem escolhidos.
Bring forward to Me the one who spilled his life on our altar.
Traga-me aquele que espirrou sua vida nesse altar.
No.
Não.
The man child.
O garoto.
Lord...
Senhor..
Why not the others?
Por que não os outros?
We will take who we will take.
Nós levaremos quem quisermos.
Rather than him, would you not prefer one who has...
Ao invés dele, você não preferiria alguém..
...hidden his fire in your sight for many years?
.. que se escondeu bem debaixo do seu nariz por muitos anos?
One who has defiled even your service?
Que traiu sua confiança?
Master!
Mestre!
Despite your flaws, you are a faithful servant.
Apesar de suas falhas, você é um servo fiel.
Now.
Agora.
We will take the one who spilled fire on our altar.
Levaremos aquele que derramou sangue no altar.
No!
Não!
You will heed our word.
Você nos ouviu.
You will not take my son!
Vocês não levarão meu filho!
You shall not fight this foe.
você não pode lutar com ele.
Come on, Jered!
Vamos, Jered!
I release you from your word.  Go!
Eu o liberto da sua promessa. Vá!
I've always wondered if you were quite as immortal as you claim.
Eu sempre me perguntei se você era tão imortal quanto dizia.
Come on!
Vamos!
I'm sorry.
Sinto muito.
He's alone up there.
Ele está lá sozinho.
What are you doing?  Go!
O que você está fazendo? Vá!
I'm not going to-
Eu não vou..
I'm not going to abandon you!
Eu não vou abandoná-lo!
Don't be a fool, boy!
Não seja idiota!
Run!
Corra!
The blood!
O sangue!
Again, boy!  Now!
De novo! Agora!Again, boy!  Agora!
Master!
Mestre!
Run!
Corra!
What!?
O que?!
It's not the blood, is it?
Não é o sangue, é?
It's my life.
É minha vida.
You can only drink the blood if I try to hold on.
Você só pode beber o sangue se eu estiver vivo.
But if I let go...
Mas se eu desistir..
Jered!
Jered!
I'll never let you have him!
Eu não permitirei!
No!
Não!
Noooooo-
Nããããooo..
Close!
Quase!
Damn you, close!
Droga, quase!
Heal, Jered!
Cure-se, Jered!
I command you, heal!
Eu te ordeno, cure-se!
Jered, live!
Jered, viva!
LIVE!
VIVA!!
Jered...
Jered...
Please.
Por favor.
Jered.
Jered.
Leave him alone!
Deixe-o em paz!
I...  I want...
Eu.. Eu quero..
He didn't spill his blood for you.
Ele não derramou sangue por você.
We shall spill our blood together...
Nós devemos derramar nosso sangue juntos..
...and by that joining we shall be made whole.
.. e dessa forma o todo se formará.
What is it?
O que é?
What are you-
O que você..
The initiation!
A iniciação!
Or, if our blood is not strong enough...
Se nosso sangue não for forte o bastante..
...we may die.
... podemos morrer.
Black monks killed my parents!
Os monges mataram meus pais!
My friends!
Meus amigos!
People die.
As pessoas morrem.
No!
Não!
You may not leave!
Você não pode ir!
I will-
Eu vou..
Go, then.
Pode ir.
C- Carrie...
C- Carrie...
We will spill our heart's blood together...
Vamos derramar juntos o sangue de nossos corações..
..and by that joining we will both be made whole.
.. e dessa forma o todo se formará.
Or if that joining is not strong enough...
Se essa união não for forte o bastante..
...we may die.
... então morreremos.
Son?
Filho?
Erm...
Erm...
It's great that we're all alright, like, but...
É superlegal que todos estejam bem...
Well, the mountain is still falling down.
Mas a montanha ainda está desabando.
Run?
Vamos correr?